<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>  
<data>  
<page>  
    <hW>AS3 HTML BOX with XML and CSS support</hW><br/>  
    <span class='disclaimer'>What Americans Want

To each according to his merit. If my theory is correct, the fairness of an economic system rests on the degree to which a participant’s fiscal condition is deserved. Americans want to earn their economic status and they want others to as well. They want to own their victories, which comes with the risk of being responsible for their defeats. Critical to this notion is the role of individual agency. A person cannot logically be celebrated for her accomplishments or panned for her disappointments if she played only a minor part in their production. There are, however, many ways to get ahead and fall behind, some of which can be pinned on the player and some of which cannot. Broadly, there are three avenues to economic success:  you can get lucky; you can benefit from some talent; you can be industrious.   The relevant difference between these paths is the degree of choice an individual has in walking them.
Chance has the smallest role for individual agency. True, you will never win the state lottery if you do not buy a lottery ticket, but the act of gambling at a gas station hardly captures the spirit of due recompense. And more often than not, the kind of luck that leads to financial ease or hardship demands no action or choice on the part of the individual. Building a trustworthy name in business and a personal fortune probably requires a bit of luck, a stroke of insight, and a fair amount of sweat. Inheriting that family name, fortune, and rolodex is an entirely different matter. Being born to this or that home is the first in a lifetime of flukes that affect our economic welfare (Bowles et al. 2005).
Talent has a middling role for agency. Be it a byproduct of genetics, parental nurturing, or a myriad other factors over which we have no direct control, some people possess aptitude for certain activities. Try as they might, my financial planner will never invest so wisely as Warren Buffett and Garfunkel will never out-compose Simon. Unlike luck, talent can be directed and honed. It may be a matter of chance that you possess some special ability, but that ability is exercised as a matter of will. Moreover, talent is often in itself insufficient to master a given pursuit. A God-given skill, while conferring considerable advantage to its holder, usually needs cultivation (Ericsson et al. 2006). Cultivation requires effort and perseverance, which, as the following paragraph argues, are largely under an individual’s control.
Industry has the meatiest role for agency. Indeed, self-help gurus and management whizzes often portray hard work as nothing but a matter of choice. Once you put yourself in the “right mindset,” productivity will shoot out your fingertips. Achieving this enlightened state, however, is not so securely under our jurisdiction. Clinical depression, anxiety, attention deficit hyperactivity disorder, chronic pain, and a host of other commonplace mental and physical impairments can rob us of our motivation. Family emergencies and unforeseen pressures may similarly take us away from economic pursuits. Nevertheless, the decision to study a foreign language daily is more reasonably attributed to personal autonomy than is having a knack for languages (talent) or having a close family member who is a native speaker (chance). A person must make a conscious choice to work diligently at some activity and commit to that choice.

    </span>  
</page>  
</data>